Brother, tell me which is the strongest rope
?
Here brother, get this brown one done.
Look brother, the kite is not to be cut.
Nonu Bhaiya, get the yellow one filled.
Hey crazy, color doesn't do anything.  Tell me
brother, how much should I pay then?
Water, ₹100 will not be enough.
Why are you asking me when you can do as you please?   Please
do it brother, just do it for ₹100.
[Music] Let's
fly this foil one first.
No, wait, we will blow it up last.
Lenny Charley's grip.
Yes, I knew you would ask me to hold the pulley.
Oh brother, get your kite ready.
Come on, let's apply it my child.
Brother, cut this one first.  First loosen up
quickly.  [MUSIC]
I said get the snakes stuffed with the yellow one.
Come on, let's go and return it.